<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yahui Zhao</title>
    <link>https://yahui624.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yahui Zhao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©Yahui 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yahui624.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Media Design Studio A&amp;B</title>
      <link>https://yahui624.github.io/media-design-studio-ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yahui624.github.io/media-design-studio-ab/</guid>
      <description>Media Design Studio A MSDA is located on Torgersen Bridge across from the software distribution desk. You can borrow different kinds of media equipment such as cameras for video or photography, GoPro, VR set, audio recorders, tripods, etc. It also rents out laptops for five days in case you need an urgent substitution for your own laptop. There are also board games, projectors, Nintendo Switch you can borrow to enjoy the hanging out time with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stroubles Creek</title>
      <link>https://yahui624.github.io/stroubles-creek/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yahui624.github.io/stroubles-creek/</guid>
      <description>Living in Lee Hall for three years and walking across Drillfield tons of times, I first heard about Stroubles Creek flowing beneath Drillfield one week ago during my Technical Writing class. Here is a brief introduction of Strouble Creek.
Location Stroubles Creek is an approximately 12-mile-long stream that runs through Virginia Tech, and Montgomery County, Virginia until it empties into the New River. Most of the sections of Stroubles Creek that flow through Blacksburg and the Virginia Tech campus are piped underground, while the portion that flows through Montgomery County is above-ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Museum Of China, Beijing</title>
      <link>https://yahui624.github.io/national-museum-of-china-beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yahui624.github.io/national-museum-of-china-beijing/</guid>
      <description>Traveling can always be exciting! Are you planning to visit China sometime in the future? Would you like to learn more about China? Today I would love to share one of my favorite places in Beijing, China.
National Museum Of China (Free entrance) Located in 16E Chang’an Avenue and was built in 1920, the National Museum of China is the third-largest art museum in the world by the gallery space, containing 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VTHacks VI</title>
      <link>https://yahui624.github.io/vthacks-vi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yahui624.github.io/vthacks-vi/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever heard about Hackathons before? Do you have awesome ideas that can make life better and easier? Are you looking forward to working with different people in groups and implementing ideas? You should definitely join VTHacks VI on the weekend of Feb 15th.
What is VTHacks VI? VTHacks VI is an all-weekend hacking &amp;amp; programming event held by VTHacks. Participants have chance to implement their ideas using programming languages to make life better and easier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Facts about Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://yahui624.github.io/fun-facts-about-raspberry-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yahui624.github.io/fun-facts-about-raspberry-pi/</guid>
      <description>What is the Raspberry Pi? The Raspberry Pi is a low cost, credit-card sized computer. The official Operating System for Raspberry Pi is called Raspbian OS, which supports most of the programming languages. More familiar operating systems can be Emteria OS (Android 7.1.2) and Windows 10 loT Core.
Why Raspberry Pi? The Raspberry Pi is first developed in the United Kingdom by the Raspberry Pi Foundation to promote the teaching of basic computer science in schools and in developing countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study smarter For Upcoming Tests before Thanksgiving break</title>
      <link>https://yahui624.github.io/study-smarter-for-upcoming-tests-before-thanksgiving-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yahui624.github.io/study-smarter-for-upcoming-tests-before-thanksgiving-break/</guid>
      <description>November is coming and there are about two weeks to Thanksgiving Holiday! We are all looking forward to the Thanksgiving break while we still have midterms, projects coming up in the upcoming weeks. Here are some tips that I hope can help you manage study better and stay happy.
Study Tips: Pay attention to the due dates and exam dates. You can save important dates on your laptop or on a notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
